{
    "subject": "Artie_Lange",
    "predicate": "actedIn",
    "object": "Artie_Lange's_Beer_League",
    "human_readable": "Artie Lange acted in Artie Lange's Beer League.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9866467714309692,
            "question": "Is Artie Lange involved in a show called 'Artie Lange's Beer League'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9699623584747314,
            "question": "Who is the star of 'Artie Lange's Beer League'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9252740144729614,
            "question": "Who created the show 'Artie Lange's Beer League'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8859694600105286,
            "question": "Is Artie Lange an actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8778558373451233,
            "question": "What kind of program is 'Artie Lange's Beer League'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8126386404037476,
            "question": "In what genre does 'Artie Lange's Beer League' fall?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7886293530464172,
            "question": "What show did Artie Lange act in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6953288316726685,
            "question": "What is Artie Lange known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5757781267166138,
            "question": "What is the name of Artie Lange's show?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5277359485626221,
            "question": "Does Artie Lange have a show of his own?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Artie Lange acted in Artie Lange's Beer League.",
            "html": "yago_26120_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Artie Lange's show?",
            "html": "yago_26120_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Artie Lange known for?",
            "html": "yago_26120_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What show did Artie Lange act in?",
            "html": "yago_26120_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26120_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26120_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26120_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26120_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26120_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26120_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26120_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26120_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26120_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26120_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information and without prior knowledge, I can evaluate whether the statement \"Artie Lange acted in Artie Lange's Beer League\" is supported by the documents.\n\nThe answer is:\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis is because all five documents mention that Artie Lange stars in the film \"Artie Lange's Beer League\", which makes its network TV premiere tonight on Comedy Central."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided context clearly states that \"Actor, comic, and Howard Stern Show cast member Artie Lange stars in the film Artie Lange's Beer League,\" which directly supports the query that Artie Lange acted in Artie Lange's Beer League."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}